<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
   <category>
      <pattern>*CRB*</pattern>
      <template>
         CRB is Connected Red Button. It gives customer capability to monitor or see scores of various matches that are telecast
		 simultaneously. For example when 8 matches of football are being telecast at the same time customer can watch one match 
		 and have clarity of scores across all other matches by pressing Red button which invokes CRB app in UI.
		 <id>F1</id>
      </template>
      
   </category>
   <category>
      <pattern>*ISP*</pattern>
      <template>
          ISP is Internet service Provider, which instructs STB that BT is the service provider and what channels or how many number 
		  of recordings can be made via STB
		  <id>F2</id>
      </template>
      
	
   </category>
    <category>
      <pattern>*DUG*</pattern>
      <template>
         DUG is Digital User Group. ISP Downloaded into STB has DUG through which one can control what channel can be displayed in UI.
		 <id>F3</id>
	  </template>
      
   </category>  
   
   <category>
		<pattern>*BUP*</pattern>
		<template>
         BUP is Broadband Usage Policy it includes broadband usage restriction of customer. E.g. If customer has unlimited subscription 
		 they will be able to use unlimited Internet whereas when customer with limited subscription package can use limited Internet as 
		 per subscription.
		 <id>F4</id>
	  </template>
	</category>  
	
	<category>
      <pattern>*D AND P*</pattern>
      <template>
		D&P stands for Directory and Profile. Whenever an order is placed via One view, a copy of it will be sent to VOSP and D and P. When 
		customer enters user name/ Password via Mobile App and attempts to login – it calls Site minder which then calls D and P to verify the 
		user details.
		<id>F5</id>
	  </template>   
    </category>
	
	
    <category>
		<pattern>*ON PERM SOLUTION AND CLOUD SOLUTION*</pattern>
		<template>
		Anything (components/ other servers) that’s built within the premises is called as On Perm and anything that’s not within the premises 
		(i.e. in Cloud) is called as cloud (e.g. AWS, Amazon web service).
		<id>F6</id>
		</template>   
	</category> 
	
	<category>
		<pattern>*CORE SITE AND GEO NODE*</pattern>
		<template>
		Core Site is in Tinsley and Rochdale environment whereas Geo site is in Baynard/ Tinsley/ Colombo/ Site 4 environments. All the App data 
		components will be deployed in Core site and channel related components are deployed in Geo site (e.g. SHM/ View Proxy).
		<id>F7</id>
		</template>   
	</category> 
	
	<category>
		<pattern>*ROOM 101*</pattern>
		<template>
		BT Corporate network is called as Green side (i.e. access restricted) and All the VOSP components are deployed in Red side (Open to Internet). 
		To prevent any of the attack from third party Room 101 acts as a bridge/ firewall between Outside Internet/ internal test environments.
		<id>F8</id>
		</template>   
	</category> 
   
   
   <category>
		<pattern>*RMP*</pattern>
		<template>
		Remote Media Processor(RMP) is a software to manage transfer or  encode media files which will then be stored in CDN (Content delivery network).
		<id>F9</id>
		</template>   
	</category> 
	
</aiml>