<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
	<category>
	
	
		<pattern>*WHAT IS THE PROJECT ALL ABOUT*</pattern>
		<template>
		This project is about testing operational and TV services delivered to BT-TV end customer. <break/>
		We carry out System Testing, End to End Testing, Headend Testing, Functional Testing, Non-Functional <break/>
		Testing and Automation Testing to ensure our client is able to deliver excellent business performance.<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC1</id>
      </template>  
	  </category> 
   <category>
   
   
      <pattern>*DIFFERENT TOOLS WE USE IN BT TV*</pattern>
      <template>
		 Major tools used in BT-TV are: <break/>
		1. Perfecto: For Web and Device Automation Testing<break/>
		2. CMS: Content Management tool which is used to create, update and edit the Web/App contents<break/>
		3. Forge: To create or update the DeltaTre IDs for Diva events <break/>
		4. OneView: To create different type of customers with different subscriptions<break/>
		5. UUI: Used as user provisioning tool for customer creation.<break/>
		6. Splunk: All the component activity logs gets captured here<break/>
		7. Storm: A tool via which we can access our STB (TV) situated at remote location (UK) <break/>
		8. Bebanjo: Content publishing tool<break/>
		9. Jira: Used for tracking the scoped in stories for the releases and ticket raised for defects.<break/>
		10. Wiki: Single source of information for scoped stories for releases and also we can find the design document for all <break/>
		programs and releases.<break/>
		11. ALM: For tracking Test Execution and defects status<break/>
		12. MPX: It’s a console where we can see all details related to content<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC2</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*WHAT RELEASE METHODOLOGY IS BEING FOLLOWED IN BT TV*</pattern>
      <template>
		BT-TV follows Agile Methodology where each sprint is around 2-3 weeks and complete Release is of 2 months. 
		 <id>GENERIC3</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*CREATE TMS PROFILE*</pattern>
      <template>
		Request you to send your details (Employee ID, Email ID, Facility ID, Deal, Entity, Phone and Address) to 
		Transport Admin or your SPOC, to create your profile in TMS. 
		 <id>GENERIC4</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*RAISE ADHOC REQUEST IN TMS*</pattern>
      <template>
		To book Adhoc cabs, please note the following procedure:<break/>
		1.Log on to the TMS tool<break/>
		2.Click on “My TMS"<break/>
		3.Click on “Raise New Adhoc"<break/>
		4.Check your employee details such as Employee I.D., Name, Manager’s Name, Facility, Entity, Deal Name and 
		Address, which get automatically populated and cannot be changed
		5.Select “Trip Type” (Pick/Drop)<break/>
		6.Select “Shift"<break/>
		7.Select the reason for Adhoc<break/>
		8.Enter the WBS element and click “Submit"<break/>
		Note: Adhoc 'pick-up' requests must be approved by the manager or nominated approving authority four hours 
		in advance from the shift selected. Adhoc 'drop-off' requests must be approved by the manager or nominated 
		approving authority an hour in advance from the shift selected.<break/>

		 <id>GENERIC5</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*DIFFERENT STAKEHOLDERS IN TV*</pattern>
      <template>
		BT Stakeholders with respective Teams are as follows:<break/>
		Sourial JR Miss (Josephine)-Headend  and M and B Team<break/>
		Daniels I Revd (Ian)- Automation, Infra and Environment<break/>
		Good NW Mr (Nick)-E2E Test Manager     <break/> 
		dAjello L Mr (Luca)-TDD and Integration Team<break/>
		Matavalam K Mr (Kedhar) -E2E Assurance and Integration Director<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC6</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*MY LINE MANAGER*</pattern>
      <template>
		Line Manager for respective teams are as follows: <break/>
		Sourial JR Miss (Josephine)-Headend Team and MandB Team<break/>
		Daniels I Revd (Ian)- Automation, Infra and Environment<break/>
		Good NW Mr (Nick)-E2E Test Manager   <break/>   
		dAjello L Mr (Luca)-TDD and Integration Team<break/>
		Matavalam K Mr (Kedhar) -E2E Assurance and Integration Director<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC7</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*DU LEAD*</pattern>
      <template>
		Balaji Venkatraman is DU lead of BT Retail. For more information on Balaji Venkatraman visit: <break/>
		<hyperlink target="_blank" href="https://people.accenture.com/People/user/balaji.venkataraman">https://people.accenture.com/People/user/balaji.venkataraman</hyperlink>
		 <id>GENERIC8</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*MD*</pattern>
      <template>
		Shrikant Sarda your MD. For more information on Shrikant Sarda  visit: <break/>
		<hyperlink target="_blank" href="https://people.accenture.com/People/user/shrikant.sarda">https://people.accenture.com/People/user/shrikant.sarda</hyperlink>
		 <id>GENERIC9</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*LOBS WE GOT IN BT*</pattern>
      <template>
		BT has Five LOBs:<break/>
		BT-TV: BT TV is an IPTV service provided by BT Plc to customers in United Kingdom With BT Broadband<break/>
		BT-Retail: The division is responsible for selling consumer services including fixed line , mobile, 
		broadband and TV.<break/>
		BT-Global Services: It delivers a combination of communications and IT services to over 5,500 organizations 
		worldwide.<break/>
		BT-Wholesale: BT Wholesale and Ventures  provides voice, broadband, data, hosted communication, managed network 
		and IT services to communications providers (CPs) in Great Britain, including BT's other divisions.<break/>
		BT-Openreach: The role of Openreach is to deliver Openreach products on an open and even handed basis to any and 
		all Communications Providers, including BT’s own “downstream” divisions, (BT Wholesale, BT Retail and BT Global Services).
		 <id>GENERIC10</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*IDEA WALL INITIATIVE*</pattern>
      <template>
		 Accenture came up with idea wall initiative where each individual can contribute an innovative idea which improvises 
		 our current process. You can share your idea on following link: <break/>
		 <hyperlink target="_blank" href="https://ts.accenture.com/sites/BTE2ETesting/Retail/BCP/Lists/Idea%20Wall_BT%20Retail/AllItems.aspx">https://ts.accenture.com/sites/BTE2ETesting/Retail/BCP/Lists/Idea%20Wall_BT%20Retail/AllItems.aspx</hyperlink>
		 <id>GENERIC11</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*FUN COMMITTEE POC*</pattern>
      <template>
		Fun committee POCs are:<break/>
		Rajesh Singh (rajesh.2.singh@bt.com)<break/>
		Bhisham Malani(bhisham.malani@bt.com)<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC12</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*ENVIRONMENT PLAN*</pattern>
      <template>
		Environment Plan is a high level plan for complete delivery of Release/s with respect to test team.
		 <id>GENERIC13</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*WHO ARE OUR CLIENTS*</pattern>
      <template>
		Our Client is BT-TV. It is an IPTV service provided by BT Plc to customers in United Kingdom with BT Broadband. <break/>
		At Accenture we responsible to carry out testing for all required services of BT-TV so that our client can deliver 
		state-of-art services to its customers.<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC14</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
   
   <category>
      <pattern>*WORK DIVIDED BETWEEN TEAMS*</pattern>
      <template>
		Work is divided between teams depending on the type of Testing is required:<break/>
		System Testing: Testing API integration between VOSP components and other Third party service providers to BT<break/>
		E2E Testing: Customer Experience testing with focus across platforms such as CCP/ VOSP/ Client/ Third Party<break/>
		Headend Testing: Network testing with focus on customer experience and channel encryption E2E flow<break/>
		Functional Testing: Testing functionality of all requirements<break/>
		Non-Functional Testing: Testing related to performance and robustness of the system<break/>
		Automation Testing: Testing using automation tools to write and execute test cases with no manual involvement.<break/>
		 <id>GENERIC14</id>
      </template>     
   </category>
</aiml>