<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<aiml>
<category>
      <pattern>NETWORK TOPOLOGY</pattern>
	   <template>
         Please refer the below diagram of Network Topology
		 <img src="topology.png" width="320" height="240"/>
		 <id>TV2</id>
      </template>
      
	</category>
	
	 <category>
      <pattern>*NETWORK DEVICES * CONNECTED TO EACH OTHER*</pattern>
      <template><srai>NETWORK TOPOLOGY</srai></template>   
   </category>
    <category>
      <pattern>*NETWORK TOPOLOGY*</pattern>
      <template><srai>NETWORK TOPOLOGY</srai></template>   
   </category>
	
   <category>
      <pattern>*ENCODER*</pattern>
      <template>
         Encoder converts analog feed into multicast IP packets and it carries out compression as well.
		 <id>HE1</id>
      </template>
      
   </category>
   <category>
      <pattern>*MULTICAST*</pattern>
      <template>
          Multicast is communication between a single sender and multiple receivers on a network. Multicast is group communication. <break/>
		  where data transmission is addressed to a group of destination computers simultaneously.
		  <id>HE2</id>
      </template>
     </category>
    <category>
      <pattern>*MPEG*</pattern>
      <template>
         MPEG is a compression standard used for compressing video and audio files to a smaller physical size, it also handles <break/>
		 the transmission of these files. Moving Picture Experts Group is the name given to the group of people responsible for <break/>
		 setting the MPEG standards. There are various adaptations of the MPEG standard each with their own specification and <break/>
		 usage in the industry.
		 <id>HE3</id>
	  </template>
      
   </category>  
   
   <category>
		<pattern>*SCRAMBLER*</pattern>
		<template>
        Scrambler is used for encryption and decryption of channels and it is integrated with CAS system at the back end.
		 <id>HE4</id>
	  </template>
	</category>  
	
	<category>
      <pattern>*CONNECT DEVICES THROUGH ITEST*</pattern>
      <template>
		iTest provides different sessions like SSH, REST API, TELNET, command prompt, By using these sessions we can connect <break/>
		to network devices through iTest
		<id>HE5</id>
	  </template>   
    </category>
	
	
    <category>
		<pattern>*PROBES*</pattern>
		<template>
		Probes are monitoring devices. It monitors video parameters like PID, CHID, Channel bandwidth etc.
		<id>HE6</id>
		</template>   
	</category>

</aiml>